(Bernadette:)Sexually.
(Raj:)Got it. Take care.
(Raj:)I guess I have no choice
(Raj:)but to make sweet,
guilt-free love to you
(Raj:)over and over again
for the rest of my life.
(Bernadette:)That's how I heard it.
Or it could be "sy-fee."
(Sheldon:)What?
S-y-F-y. "Sy-fee."
(Raj:)Oh, right.
(Raj:)Good one.
(Penny:)So, did you get a chance
to go over the scene I gave you?
(Sheldon:)Yes. I didn't care for it.
Okay, Cat on a Hot Tin Roof
is an American classic.
(Sheldon:)So is the McRib sandwich.
(Sheldon:)I don't care
for that, either.
(Penny:)Fine. What would you rather do
as a scene study?
(Sheldon:)I'm glad you asked.
(Sheldon:)I took the liberty
of adapting a Star Trek
fan fiction novella
(Sheldon:)I wrote when I was ten